<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<dataroot>
  <Report>
    <Image>reports</Image>
    <Description>Business Centric Reports</Description>
  </Report>
  <Report>
    <Image></Image>
    <Description>Excel, Word, Presentation, PDF and PDF Viewer are industry wide standards for creating and sharing reports. Build your reporting solution on our standards based, easy to use solution.</Description>
  </Report>
  <Report>
    <Image>ease</Image>
    <Description>Ease of Use</Description>
  </Report>
  <Report>
    <Image></Image>
    <Description>Feel at home with Visual Studio when you develop with Syncfusion controls. Full Visual Studio integration, additional utilities for effectively managing integrating the controls and an intuitive object model all mean increased productivity.</Description>
  </Report>
  <Report>
    <Image>perform</Image>
    <Description>Unmatched performance</Description>
  </Report>
  <Report>
    <Image></Image>
    <Description>Native .NET code libraries built for delivering reports with unmatched performance. Deploy with confidence and process millions of rows of data in server and desktop environments.</Description>
  </Report>
  <Report>
    <Image>office</Image>
    <Description>Office not required</Description>
  </Report>
  <Report>
    <Image></Image>
    <Description>All our reporting solutions are completely independent libraries that have no dependencies on Microsoft Office or Adobe Acrobat.</Description>
  </Report>
  <Report>
    <Image>support</Image>
    <Description>Best of industry support</Description>
  </Report>
  <Report>
    <Image></Image>
    <Description>With our sophisticated Direct Trac support system built from the ground up to support enterprise customers, you will have a streamlined experience working with our support team.</Description>
  </Report>
  <Report>
    <Image>license</Image>
    <Description>Hassle free licensing</Description>
  </Report>
  <Report>
    <Image></Image>
    <Description>Our licensing options can fit whatever your project needs. We offer everything from per user licensing, to site licenses that cover all the users in one building, to global licenses. We offer simple, hassle free licensing, with no royalties or server deployment charges.</Description>
  </Report>
  <Report>
    <Image>source</Image>
    <Description>Full source code</Description>
  </Report>
  <Report>
    <Image></Image>
    <Description>When you work with Syncfusion, complete, easy to work with source code is available for all components. We also ensure that the source code can be used with a minimum of effort. The availability of source code also makes our products easier to extend and helps users to build reusable frameworks.</Description>
  </Report>
</dataroot>